Narrator: have
A: Do you have a pet?
What is it?
How long have you had it?
B: Do you have a tablet?
What kind?
How long have you had it?
Narrator: live
A: Do you live in a modern flat?
How old is it?
How long have you lived there?
B: Do you live near this school?
Where exactly?
How long have you lived there?
Narrator: know
A: Do you know anybody from another country?
Where’s he or she from?
How long have you known him or her?
Narrator: be
B: Are you a fan of a football team?
Which team?
How long have you been a fan?
A: Are you a member of a club or organization?
Which one?
How long have you been a member?
B: Are you married?
What’s your partner’s name?
How long have you been married?